[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are Benny and Joon related in the movie of the same name?", "correct_answer": "They are brother and sister.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are just friends.", "They are cousins.", "They are boyfriend and girlfriend."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following languages is spoken as primary language by the most people?", "correct_answer": "Bengali", "incorrect_answers": ["German", "Italian", "Russian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A person with this disorder has fluctuating levels of orientation.", "correct_answer": "Delirium", "incorrect_answers": ["Dementia", "Psychosis", "Delusional State"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the most active volcano in Mexico, located mostly in the Mexican state of Jalisco?", "correct_answer": "Colima", "incorrect_answers": ["Nevado de Toluca", "Barcena", "Las Cumbres"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the gestation period of a beaver?", "correct_answer": "4 months", "incorrect_answers": ["2 months", "3 months", "6 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Im sorry Dave, Im afraid I cant do that.  This memorable line of dialogue comes from which film?", "correct_answer": "2001 - A Space Odyssey", "incorrect_answers": ["Tron", "Alien", "Battlestar Gallactica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest mountain in the western hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "Aconcagua", "incorrect_answers": ["McKinley", "Pissis", "K2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phylum do jellyfish belong to?", "correct_answer": "Cnidaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Arthropoda", "Chordata", "Mollusca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the tagline on the theatrical poster of the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?", "correct_answer": "Dark secrets revealed", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Evil has never been so close", "The battle between the darkness and the light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you want to remove graffiti from the wall of your house, you should do it within this period of time.", "correct_answer": "24-48 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["1 week", "48-72 hours", "6 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the term denoting a group of zebras that live together?", "correct_answer": "Harem", "incorrect_answers": ["Pack", "Stud", "Herd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of what descent is Drew Barrymores father, John Drew Barrymore?", "correct_answer": "Irish", "incorrect_answers": ["Danish", "Russian", "Jewish"]}]